Taylor Roberts

Implementation Analyst / Accounting Specialist

El Cajon, CA 92020 taylorroberts743_7nf@indeedemail.com (760) 552-2258

Highly focused, self-motivated accounting professional with exceptional attention to detail and possesses advanced knowledge of G/L accounting and GAAP principles. Operates with a strong sense of urgency and

thrives in a fast-paced setting. Resourceful team-member with demonstrable client service excellence.

Work Experience

Implementation Analyst

MULTI-FAMILY UTILITY COMPANY - San Diego, CA February 2019 to Present

- Actively implement utility billing for national clients, ensuring accurate billing of all contracted services in accordance with federal, state, and local ordinances
- Conduct billing analysis and rate analysis with careful audit controls and act as the resource expert
- Coordinate and engage in cross-team meetings with the MUC and Project teams with high involvement on the implementation timeline for client and ensuring service excellence.
- · Well-versed at resolving moderately complex billing and system inquiries and discrepancies including

confidential and sensitive information (employing both text and discretion)

· Strong record of cultivating and maintaining outstanding relationships with clients

Service Center Representative (Contract)

KAISER PERMANENTE - San Diego, CA October 2018 to February 2019

Maintained member data with high quality assurance and efficiently processed health plan enrollments,

corrections, retroactivity adjustments and terminations

• Researched, reconciled and resolved billing discrepancies with keen accuracy made on member eligibility

determination and payment delinquencies

- Collected and ensured customer service quality measures were exceeded
- Active participation on cross-team collaborative projects and contributed to customer service and operations improvements initiatives

Bookkeeping Assistant

BENOIST DRAINS & PLUMBING, INC - San Diego, CA June 2016 to November 2017

- Created customer invoices, post payments and deposits via QuickBooks
- Maintained data security of record-keeping; ensured financial data back-up; remitted secured electronic

files to owners

• Assisted in filing duties and provided technical assistance

Financial Aid Student Intake Assistant

HUMBOLDT STATE UNIVERSITY - Arcata, CA March 2015 to May 2016

- Conveyed general information to aid recipients on maintaining financial aid eligibility
- · Assisted students, parents, staff, and faculty with information on complex financial aid programs
- Interpreted financial aid application results and promptly responded to questions and concerns from students and parents that lead to resourceful alternatives of coverage
- Collected, stored, and managed student aid files via Nolij's with high degree of confidentiality and integrity

Education

Bachelor of Science in Accounting

California State University - Los Angeles, CA 2018

Skills

- Receptionist
- database
- Excel
- accounting
- Microsoft Excel
- MS Office
- Data Entry
- Bookkeeping
- Accounts Payable
- QuickBooks
- · General Ledger Accounting